bikerornot.com 2010-05-13

# Biker Or Not - 100% Free Biker Dating and Social Networking.

  **BikerOrNot.com Privacy Policy**

BikerOrNot.com is an online service that allows our members to set up unique personal profiles that can be linked together through networks of friends. BikerOrNot members can view each others' profiles, communicate with old friends and meet new friends on the service, share photos, post journals and comments, and describe their interests. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. BikerOrNot members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them. 

Information Collection and Use by BikerOrNot.com 

BikerOrNot.com collects user submitted information such as email address and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the BikerOrNot.com service. BikerOrNot.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, and  age  in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

BikerOrNot.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes 

User Profile information including members' pictures are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the BikerOrNot.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join BikerOrNot, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on BikerOrNot.com with each other through the BikerOrNot.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. 

Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members

BikerOrNot members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. BikerOrNot.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations BikerOrNot.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. 

 Use of Cookies 

BikerOrNot.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from BikerOrNot.com in order to use most functions on the site. 

 Links 

BikerOrNot.com contains links to sites. BikerOrNot.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on BikerOrNot.com. 

 Chat Rooms, Journals and WebLogs, Message Boards and Public Forums 

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards  or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

 Correcting/Updating or Removing Information 

BikerOrNot.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. 

 Security 

BikerOrNot.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords BikerOrNot.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

 Sharing and Disclosure of Information BikerOrNot.com Collects 

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, BikerOrNot will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by BikerOrNot.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the BikerOrNot.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. BikerOrNot reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of BikerOrNot or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

 Changes in Our Privacy Policy 

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

 Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy@BikerOrNot.com (475 Central Avenue Suite 302, Saint Petersburg, FL 33701)
